We ask a very basic question here.
We ask, do you think American society is racist?
And there is actually widespread in our poll agreement that it is 50, nearly 60 percent, 59 percent saying yes.
And if you take a look here and just break this down by race, there is a majority.
It's a smaller majority, but a majority of white Americans feel that way.
And then larger majorities of African-Americans and Hispanics feel the same way, too.
So on the question of is America racist, you're getting that nearly 60 percent of the country saying yes.
We're not a racist country, Brian. We've never been a racist country.
No, I don't think America is a racist country.
America is not a racist country.
So we should stop arguing about whether or not this is a racist country. It is not.